<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GDG Kisii</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">My GDG</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_feed">Feed</string>
    <string name="title_info">Info</string>
    <string name="title_intro">Welcome To GDG Kisii</string>
    <string name="title_hometext">We are GDG Kisii</string>
    <string name="title_splash">Learn ▪ Collaborate ▪ Share</string>
    <string name="what_title">What is a GDG? </string>
    <string name="what_desc">Google is known all around the world.
        Everyone is Googling, checking on Maps and communicating on Gmail.
        For simple users, they are services that work for them, but not for us.
        Developers see much more: APIs, Scalability issues, complex technology stacks and that is what GDG is about.
        Basically, a Google Developer Group (GDG) is a community of tech enthusiasts, developers, designers and creators
        who are interested in learning more about Google developer technology and tools. GDGs are focused on developers and
        technical content.</string>
    <string name="what2_title">What is GDG Kisii?</string>
    <string name="what2_desc">GDG Kisii is an active developer ecosystem comprising of self-motivated
        tech enthusiasts, developers and creators. If you would like to dive deeper into Google developer
        technologies; everything from Android, Firebase, Chrome, App Engine, HTML5 to product APIs like the
        YouTube API, Maps API and Chart Tools then this is the right place to be. Are you stuck, worried about
        whether to use web apps or mobile apps, tabs or double spaces, material design or flat design, we discuss code,
        best practices, the pros and cons and whatever else goes into implementing state of the art applications using Google
        Developer technology.</string>


</resources>
